I've been trying to get a ride for three hours
so i decided to change my strategy
only it's the city I want to go to
but that talks a lot more about me than the driver
so I decided to improve this sentence a little bit
and see if it works
calm there
do you think this can work
hi there's good guy
beauty beauty
you don't go to the outside judge you know
ride for me no boy
thank you too much
know who you can trust
always stay
everyone has a flea behind their ear
guy you used the car drawing to show
the word car too
I was so kind of surprised
stayed until
not knowing what to say
I leave it closer to the destination where I'm going
that there I chose 1 hunting city like that on the map
oh it is and I will do 1 challenge
I'll arrive in town with R$1
and I have 30 days to set up 1 business
without knowing anyone
I don't know anyone